Guide to the Charles Seymour, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and subject files, 1917-1954 1937-1950; 1937-1950; Series I
  - University Council, 1937-1950 (Box 163, Folder 1375)
    - Committee on the Division of Medical Affairs, 1948-1950 (Box 163, Folder 1383)
    - Committee on the Division of the Sciences, 1947-1948 (Box 163, Folder 1384)
    - Committee on Engineering, 1948-1950 (Box 163, Folder 1385)
    - Committee on the Forestry School, 1948-1949 (Box 163, Folder 1386)
    - Committee on the Law School, 1947-1950 (Box 163, Folder 1387)
    - Committee on the Law School, 1947-1950 (Box 164, Folder 1388)
    - Committee on the Library, 1948-1950 (Box 164, Folder 1389)
    - Committee on Military and Naval Affairs, 1948-1949 (Box 164, Folder 1390)
    - Committee on the Music School, 1947-1949 (Box 164, Folder 1391)
    - Committee on Peabody Museum, 1947-1950 (Box 164, Folder 1392)
    - Committee on Publications, 1937-1939, 1948-1950 (Box 164, Folder 1393)
    - Committee on Religious Life & Study, 1948-1949 (Box 164, Folder 1394)
    - Committee on Social Sciences, 1949-1950 (Box 164, Folder 1395)
    - Committee on University Development, 1947-1949 (Box 164, Folder 1396-1397)
      See also: box 165, folder 1404
    - Corporation By-Law, proposal to replace #55, undated (Box 164, Folder 1398)
    - Correspondence and lists, 1947-1949 (Box 164, Folder 1399-1400)
    - Executive Committee: agendas, minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 165, Folder 1401)
    - Letters of comment, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 1402)
    - Letters to Deans, Directors, Officers etc., 1947-1948 (Box 165, Folder 1403)
    - Listening Posts [local representatives of Committee on University Development], 1948-1949 (Box 165, Folder 1404)
    - Lists, extra copies, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 1405)
    - Meeting [1st], 1948 February 22 (Box 165, Folder 1406)
    - Meeting [2nd], 1948 May 15 (Box 165, Folder 1407)
    - Meeting [3rd], 1948 November 19-20 (Box 165, Folder 1408)
    - Meeting, 1949 May 6-7, July 27 (Box 165, Folder 1409)
    - Meeting, 1949 October 28 (Box 165, Folder 1410)
    - Meeting, 1950 May 5 (Box 165, Folder 1411)
    - Resolutions and recommendations to the Corporation, 1948-1950 (Box 165, Folder 1412)
    - Statements describing council, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 1413)
    - Statistics, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 1414)
  - University Development Committee
    See: box 129, folder 1092 See: box 164, folder 1396-1397
  - University Development, 1944-1950
    - Alumni Board, C. R. Beardsley, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 1415)
    - Alumni Fund, Samuel S. Duryee, 1944-1947 (Box 165, Folder 1416)
    - Committee on Endowment and Gifts, 1948-1950 (Box 165, Folder 1417)
      - Alumni Class Gift Committee, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 1418)
      - Local Committee on University Development, 1948-1950 (Box 165, Folder 1419)
      - University Needs, Yale brochure, 1947-1950 (Box 165, Folder 1420-1421)
    - Committee to Organize a Division of University Development, 1946-1947 (Box 166, Folder 1422)
    - Committee for the Sciences, 1944-1947 (Box 166, Folder 1423)
    - [New] Endowment Fund Campaign, 1945-1947 (Box 166, Folder 1424)
    - Office of University Development, 1947-1950 (Box 166, Folder 1425)
      - Alumni News Releases, 1948-1949 (Box 166, Folder 1426)
      - Howard W. Haggard, 1948 (Box 166, Folder 1427)
      - President"s first letter to alumni, 1949 (Box 166, Folder 1428)
      - President"s second letter to alumni, 1949-1950 (Box 166, Folder 1429)
    - Report to the President on Procedures for Raising Funds [Haggard], 1947 (Box 166, Folder 1430)
  - University Health, Board of: minutes, reports of the Sanitary Inspector, 1937-1950 (Box 167, Folder 1431)
  - University Policy, 1938-1950 (Box 167, Folder 1432)
  - V, 1937-1950 (Box 167, Folder 1433-1436)
  - Vaill, George Dudley
    See: box 5, folder 36
  - Van Santvoord, George, 1938-1949 (Box 168, Folder 1437)
  - Veterans (returned) and dislocated war workers, Guidance Center for [Post War P.B., Yale University, Inst. Human Relations, NH War Council], 1944 (Box 168, Folder 1438)
  - VIF - Intercollegiate French Review, 1938-1939 (Box 168, Folder 1439)
  - Vocational Counseling Service, Inc., 1948 (Box 168, Folder 1439a)
  - Vocational Counseling Service, Inc. [Post-War Planning Board], 1945 (Box 168, Folder 1440)
  - Wab - Wal, 1937-1950 (Box 168, Folder 1441-1443)
  - Walker, Charles R., 1944-1947 (Box 168, Folder 1444)
  - Wam - Wan, 1937-1950 (Box 168, Folder 1445)
  - Wam - Wan, 1937-1950 (Box 169, Folder 1446-1448)
  - War casualties: letters of sympathy for, 1943-1945 (Box 169, Folder 1449)
  - War Memorial Tablets: dedication service, 1950 February 22 (Box 169, Folder 1450)
  - War Memorials Committee
    See: box 54, folder 473
  - War prisoners [POW], 1944-1945 (Box 169, Folder 1451)
  - Charles H. Warren Student Loan Fund, 1945 (Box 169, Folder 1452)
  - Lewis Baker Warren Memorial Foundation [Charles Howard Warren], 1922-1923, 1935-1936 (Box 169, Folder 1453)
  - Lewis Baker Warren Memorial Scholarship, 1940 (Box 169, Folder 1454)
  - Wea - Wei, 1937-1950 (Box 169, Folder 1455)
  - Weed, Dr. Lewis Hill, 1946-1949 (Box 170, Folder 1456)
  - Wel - Wer, 1937-1950 (Box 170, Folder 1457)
  - Wes - Wet, 1937-1950 (Box 170, Folder 1458-1459)
  - Westinghouse Educational Foundation
    See: box 65, folder 568
  - Wh, 1937-1950 (Box 170, Folder 1460-1461)
  - Whitridge, Arnold
    See: box 156, folder 1310
  - Wic - Wilk, 1937-1950 (Box 170, Folder 1462)
  - Wickersham, General C.W. [The School of Military Government], 1942-1944 (Box 170, Folder 1463)
  - Wiggin and Dana, 1938-1948 (Box 170, Folder 1464)
  - Will - Wilm, 1937-1950 (Box 171, Folder 1464-1466)
  - Williams College [President James Phinny Baxter], 1937-1943, 1948 (Box 171, Folder 1467)
  - Wilkie, Wendell
    - Democrats for Wilkie material, 1940 (Box 171, Folder 1468)
    - Letters concerning Seymour"s article, 1940 (Box 171, Folder 1469)
    - Weymour"s article on Wilkie for, 1940 (Box 171, Folder 1470)
  - Wils - Wit, 1937-1950 (Box 171, Folder 1471-1473)
  - Duke of Windsor"s visit [Institute of International Studies], 1943 November 2 (Box 172, Folder 1474)
  - Winternitz, Dr. Milton C., undated (Box 172, Folder 1475)
  - Wo, 1937-1950 (Box 172, Folder 1476-1479)
  - Wolfers, Arnold
    See: box 159, folder 1342
  - Women Students
    See: box 147, folder 1241
  - Women's Dormitory [proposed], 1942 (Box 172, Folder 1480)
  - Woodcock, H.F.
    See: box 25, folder 210
  - Woodward Lectureship, 1937-1949 (Box 172, Folder 1481)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1938-1948 (Box 172, Folder 1482)
  - Wr - Wy, 1937-1950 (Box 172, Folder 1483)
  - WRUL broadcasts, 1944 (Box 172, Folder 1484)
  - X - Y - Z, 1937-1950 (Box 173, Folder 1485-1486)
  - Yale, Elihu, 1942-1948 (Box 173, Folder 1487)
    - 300th Anniversary of Birth, 1948-1949 (Box 173, Folder 1488)
  - Yale Alumni University Fund Association
    See: box 8, folder 71-74 See: box 9, folder 75-77
  - Yale Association of Japan
    See: box 90, folder 772
  - Yale Bowl
    See: box 25, folder 207
  - Yale Clubs
    See: box 2, folder 17-18 See: box 3, folder 19-23
  - Yale College
    See: box 44, folder 371-373
  - Yale Community Budget Drive
  - Yale Community Council, 1938-1942 (Box 173, Folder 1490)
  - Yale Daily News, 1937-1950 (Box 173, Folder 1491-1492)
  - Yale Farms [including United Nationals Organization site correspondence], 1946 (Box 173, Folder 1493)
  - Yale Football Y Association
    See: box 25, folder 208
  - Yale-Harvard-Princeton Conference on Public Affairs, 1937-1938 (Box 174, Folder 1494)
  - Yale-in-China, 1937-1950 (Box 174, Folder 1495-1498)
  - Yale-in-China: Committee on President Wei"s visit to Yale, 1937-1938 (Box 174, Folder 1499)
  - Yale-in-China: minutes, 1936-1939 (Box 175, Folder 1500)
  - Yale in Publication; Yale University Press and Yale Review, undated (Box 175, Folder 1501)
  - Yale plates, 1940 (Box 175, Folder 1502)
  - Yale Political Union, 1937-1950 (Box 175, Folder 1503)
  - Yale-Reid Hall Summer Program
    See: box 72, folder 621
  - Yale Scholarship Trust of Chicago
    See: box 34, folder 302
  - Yale Review
    See: box 179, folder 1545
  - Yale studies for returning servicemen, 1944-1947 (Box 175, Folder 1504-1506)
  - Yale University, 1937-1950
    - 250th Anniversary celebration, 1947-1950 (Box 175, Folder 1507)
    - Coat of Arms, 1947 (Box 175, Folder 1508)
    - Committee on Educational Costs, 1935-1937 (Box 175, Folder 1509)
    - Committee on Educational Planning, 1937-1946 (Box 175, Folder 1510-1511)
    - Committee on Educational Planning, 1937-1946 (Box 176, Folder 1512)
      - Minutes, 1937-1940 (Box 176, Folder 1513)
    - Committee on Enrollment and Scholarships, 1944-1949 (Box 176, Folder 1514)
    - Committee on Grants for Scientific Research, 1943-1945 (Box 176, Folder 1515)
    - Committee on Honorary Degrees, 1937-1950 (Box 176, Folder 1516-1520)
    - (Advisory) Committee on Labor Relations: personnel director, 1942-1944 (Box 177, Folder 1521)
    - Committee on Lectures, 1937-1950 (Box 177, Folder 1522)
    - Committee on Liberal Studies, 1943-1944 (Box 177, Folder 1523)
    - Committee on the Library: staff and appointments, 1937-1950 (Box 177, Folder 1524)
    - Committee on Memorials, 1938-1942 (Box 177, Folder 1525)
    - Committee on Personnel Problems: personnel director, 1939-1940 (Box 177, Folder 1526)
    - Committee on Post-War Planning, 1942 (Box 177, Folder 1527)
      See also: Series II
    - Committee on Transportation, 1940-1943 (Box 177, Folder 1528)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Activities, 1937-1950 (Box 177, Folder 1529-1530)
    - Committee on University Personnel Policy: personnel director, 1946-1947 (Box 177, Folder 1531)
    - Committee to Study the Post-War Relationship of the University to the Community, 1945 (Box 177, Folder 1532)
    - History, 1938-1950 (Box 177, Folder 1533)
      - World War II: Roll of Honor, 1945-1948 (Box 177, Folder 1534)
    - Yale University Press, 1938-1950 (Box 178, Folder 1535-1539)
      - Committee to Consider Yale Sponsorship of the Chronicles of American Photoplays etc., 1944-1950 (Box 178, Folder 1540)
      - Committee to Report on the Work of Yale Press (Corporation), 1943-1944 (Box 178, Folder 1541)
      - Committee to Study Methods of Distribution of Photoplays and Slides and Reports thereon, 1945 (Box 178, Folder 1542)
      - Governing Board, 1938-1950 (Box 178, Folder 1543)
      - Governing Board, 1938-1950 (Box 179, Folder 1544)
      - Yale Review, 1938-1950 (Box 179, Folder 1545)
  - Yerkes Laboratory of Primate Biology, Inc., 1937-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1546-1548)
  - Yerkes Laboratory of Primate Biology, Inc., 1937-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1549-1550)
    - Administrative Committee, 1939-1942 (Box 180, Folder 1551)
    - Annual meetings, 1941-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1552)
    - Annual reports, 1938-1941 (Box 180, Folder 1553)
    - Anthropoid Research Station: purchase of land and construction, 1929-1931 (Box 180, Folder 1554)
    - Minutes, 1937-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1555)
    - Scientific Advisory Board, 1939 (Box 181, Folder 1556)
  - YMCA: Dwight Hall, 1936-1950 (Box 181, Folder 1557-1559)
    - International and Foreign Relations groups, 1938-1950 (Box 181, Folder 1560)
    - Luther Tucker, 1942-1949 (Box 181, Folder 1561)
    - Yale Community Budget Drive Committee, 1937-1950 (Box 181, Folder 1562)
  - YMCA: New Haven and National, 1938-1950 (Box 181, Folder 1563)
  - Zoology, Department of, 1937-1950 (Box 181, Folder 1564)
- War emergency planning records, 1938-1947; Series II
  - "Aid for the Allies": broadcast, 1940 June 22 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Army Air Force, 1942 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Technical Training Command, 1942-1945 (Box 182, Folder 3-4)
  - Army Enlisted Reserves: Joint Enlistment Board, 1942-1943 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Army medical education, 1943 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Army Officers Detachment: substituted by reserve or retired officers, 1940 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Army Service Forces, 1945-1946 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Army Specialized Training Program, 1942-1946 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Army Specialized Training Program, 1942-1946 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Comments on, 1943 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - For medical students at the Medical School, 1943-1946 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Army Specialized and Navy Collegiate Training Program, 1942-1943 (Box 183, Folder 13-14)
  - Army and Navy Staff College, 1946 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Aviation Cadet Program, 1942-1943 (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - British Children - Yale Committee, 1940-1948 (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - British Universities: greetings sent to Oxford and Cambridge, 1940-1943 (Box 183, Folder 18)
  - Chatham broadcast, 1941 (Box 183, Folder 19)
  - Civil Affairs Training School, 1943-1945 (Box 183, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Industrial Medicine, 1940-1942 (Box 183, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Physical Training for War Service, 1942-1944 (Box 184, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Post-War Planning and Reconstruction, 1942-1944 (Box 184, Folder 23)
    - New England Regional Planning Program, 1942-1945 (Box 184, Folder 24)
    - Subcommittee on Educational Planning, 1942-1943 (Box 184, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Preparation for War Service: curricula, 1942-1943 (Box 184, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1943 (Box 184, Folder 27)
    - Pamphlets, 1942 (Box 184, Folder 28)
  - Committee on War Risk Insurance, 1942-1943 (Box 184, Folder 29)
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1940-1941 (Box 184, Folder 30-31)
  - Committee to Study the Post-War Relationship of the University to the Community, 1944 (Box 184, Folder 32)
  - Engineering Program - National Defense, 1940-1945 (Box 185, Folder 33-34)
  - Epidemic diseases in the Army, investigation of, 1941 (Box 185, Folder 35)
  - Faculty: leaves of absence during the war and promotions following the war, 1943-1945 (Box 185, Folder 36)
  - General war folder, 1940-1943 (Box 185, Folder 37-38)
  - Government contracts, 1941-1942 (Box 185, Folder 39)
  - History of discussions and negotiations between the University and the Armed Forces, 1943 (Box 185, Folder 40)
  - History of war: preparation, 1942-1943 (Box 185, Folder 41)
  - King"s College, Cambridge: windows, services, 1940, 1945 (Box 185, Folder 42)
  - Letters to President Seymour from Yale men overseas, 1944-1945 (Box 185, Folder 43)
  - Letters to Presidents of Colleges and Universities, 1940-1941 (Box 185, Folder 44)
  - (U.S.) Marine Corps, 1938-1943 (Box 186, Folder 45)
    - Letters regarding applications to, 1940-1943 (Box 186, Folder 46)
  - Medical School: affiliation with the U.S. Army Surgical Hospital No. 39, 1940-1944 (Box 186, Folder 47)
  - Memorials to Yale men killed in WW II: proposed, 1945-1950 (Box 186, Folder 48)
  - Military Training Camp Association, 1940 (Box 186, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1946 (Box 186, Folder 50)
  - National Defense Research Committee (O.S.R.D.), 1941-1946 (Box 186, Folder 51)
  - National Research Council, 1940-1945
    - Committee on Treatment of Gas Casualties, 1941-1942 (Box 186, Folder 52)
    - Division of Medical Sciences, Sub-Committee on Historical Records, 1940-1942 (Box 186, Folder 53)
    - Canada, 1945 (Box 186, Folder 54)
  - National War College, 1946-1947 (Box 186, Folder 55)
  - (U.S.) Naval Reserves, 1939-1943 (Box 186, Folder 56-57)
    See also: box 187, folder 67
  - Naval Training Program, 1940 (Box 186, Folder 58)
  - Navy College Training Program, 1943-1946 (Box 186, Folder 59)
  - Navy College Training Program, 1943-1946 (Box 187, Folder 60-63)
  - (U.S.) Navy Department, 1941-1946 (Box 187, Folder 64)
    - Advisory Committee on Officer Procurement and Training in the Colleges, 1942-1945 (Box 187, Folder 65)
    - "Buying A Navy", 1946 May (Box 187, Folder 66)
  - Navy Enlisted Reserve Class V-1 and V-7, 1941-1942 (Box 187, Folder 67)
  - Navy Programs: E.D.S., 1943 (Box 188, Folder 68)
  - Navy V-12: facilities questionnaire, 1942-1943 (Box 188, Folder 69)
  - Neurotropic Viruses, Commission on: government contract, 1941 (Box 188, Folder 70)
  - New Haven Civilian Defense Committee, 1941-1943 (Box 188, Folder 71)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1942-1945 (Box 188, Folder 72)
  - Office for Emergency Management, 1942 (Box 188, Folder 73)
  - Office of War Information, 1942-1944 (Box 188, Folder 74)
  - Office of War Mobilization and Reconversion, 1945-1946 (Box 188, Folder 75)
  - Programs and religion in the services, 1943-1945 (Box 188, Folder 76)
  - Science needs, post-war, 1945-1947 (Box 188, Folder 77)
  - Selective Service, 1940-1945 (Box 188, Folder 78)
  - Selective Service, 1940-1945 (Box 189, Folder 79)
    - 18-19 Draft Law, 1942 (Box 189, Folder 80)
    - Registration under the Selective Service and Training Act, 1940, 1942 (Box 189, Folder 81)
  - Staff Officers Asiatic Studies Course, 1945-1946 (Box 189, Folder 82)
  - State Defense - Graves Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 189, Folder 83)
  - Undergraduate Colleges and the Armed Forces: relationship between, 1943-1944 (Box 189, Folder 84)
  - Undergraduate War Council, 1942 (Box 189, Folder 85)
  - United States Armed Forces Institute, 1943-1944 (Box 189, Folder 86)
  - United States Departments of Education and Commerce, American Council on Education National Defense, 1940-1946 (Box 189, Folder 87-89)
    - American Council on Education National Defense, 1940-1946 (Box 190, Folder 90)
  - United States destroyers for Britain, 1940 (Box 190, Folder 91)
  - United States State Department, 1942 (Box 190, Folder 92)
    - War Department: U.S. Army, 1940-1946 (Box 190, Folder 93-95)
  - Universal military training, 1940 (Box 190, Folder 96)
  - Universities in wartime, British and American, 1942 (Box 190, Folder 97)
  - University Defense Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 190, Folder 98)
  - University War Council: Mr. Charles R. Walker, Secretary, 1942-1943 (Box 190, Folder 99)
    - Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 190, Folder 100)
  - V-E Day Plans, V-J Day Plans [Memorial Service], 1944-1945 (Box 190, Folder 101)
  - Victory Book Campaign, 1942 (Box 190, Folder 102)
  - War Collection (Library), 1939-1942, 1945 (Box 190, Folder 103)
  - War Collection (Library), 1939-1942, 1945 (Box 191, Folder 104-106)
  - War degrees, 1941-1943 (Box 191, Folder 107)
  - War Manpower Commission: Office of Emergency Management, 1942-1943 (Box 191, Folder 108)
    - National Roster of Scientific and Specialized Personnel, 1941-1944 (Box 191, Folder 109)
      - Manual of operations, 1942 September 24 (Box 191, Folder 110)
  - War service (faculty): lists, etc., 1940-1944 (Box 191, Folder 111-112)
  - War service (faculty): lists, etc., 1940-1944 (Box 192, Folder 113)
  - War statistics, 1942-1947 (Box 192, Folder 114)
  - Warren Committee: Committee on Research in Physical Science and Engineering [National Academy of Sciences] [National Research Council], 1940-1941 (Box 192, Folder 115)
  - Wartime Administrative Problems, Conference on: sponsored by Connecticut"s and Yale"s Departments of Education and New Haven State Teachers College, 1943 (Box 192, Folder 116)
  - Yale - Harvard - Princeton National Defense, 1940-1943 (Box 192, Folder 117)
- Post-war planning board records, 1943-1945; Series III
  - American Society of Planning Officials, 1943 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Baldwin, Governor Raymond E., 1943-1945 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Bills relating to recommendations of the Post-War Planning Board passed by the 1945 General Assembly, undated (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - By-Laws, 1943 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Chairman of the Board: Charles Seymour, letters to board members and committee chairmen regarding his resignation as chairman, undated (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Chairman of the Board: Albert Waugh, 1945 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Community Development and Housing, 1943-1944 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education, 1943-1944 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Finance, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Industry and Labor, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Medical Care and Health, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Public Information, undated (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Public Utilities and Transportation, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Public Works, 1944 (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - Sub-Committee on Water Conservation and Sanitation, 1944 (Box 194, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Recreation, 1944 (Box 194, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Rural Life and Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box 194, Folder 18)
  - Committee to Consider Land Use Problems, 1944 (Box 194, Folder 19)
  - Committees: suggestions for personnel, 1943-1944 (Box 194, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Associations, Planning and Zoning Agencies, Industrial, etc., 1943 (Box 194, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Intergovernmental Cooperation: Judge Henry Hunt, Director, 1943 (Box 194, Folder 22)
    - State Development Commission, William B. Rogers, Chairman, 1943-1945 (Box 194, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut, Post-War
      See: box 197, folder 70
    - Public Expenditure Council, Inc., 1944, undated (Box 194, Folder 24)
    - Reemployment Commission, 1943-1945 (Box 194, Folder 25-27)
    - Reemployment Commission: Reemployment [magazine], 1944-1945 (Box 195, Folder 28)
    - State State Housing Authority Prentice White, Administrator, 1943 (Box 195, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut State Journal, 1943 September (Box 195, Folder 30)
      See also: box 199, folder 75
    - University of, 1945 January (Box 195, Folder 31)
    - War Council, 1943-1944 (Box 195, Folder 32)
      - Committee on Education. [C.S., a member, resigned 1/3/45], 1943-1945 (Box 195, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence
    See also: box 197, folder 63
    - with Connecticut Senators and Congressmen in regard to the Planning Board, 1943-1944 (Box 195, Folder 34)
    - with members and personnel of the committees, 1943-1944 (Box 195, Folder 35-36)
  - Council of State Governments, 1944 (Box 195, Folder 37)
  - Crapo, Herbert L.
    See: box 196, folder 43-44
  - Creation of the Board: legislative acts, 1943 (Box 195, Folder 38)
  - Dana, Arnold Guyot
    See: box 197, folder 66
  - Director of Research, George A. Dudley, 1943-1945 (Box 195, Folder 39)
  - Drafting Committee, undated (Box 196, Folder 40)
  - Dudley, George A.
    See: box 195, folder 39
  - Educational Programs, 1943 (Box 196, Folder 41)
  - Executive Committee, 1944 (Box 196, Folder 42)
  - Executive Director: Herbert L. Crapo, 1943-1944 (Box 196, Folder 43-44)
  - Executive Director and Director of Research: Letters regarding, 1943 (Box 196, Folder 45)
  - Expenses: [University Expense Acct. for], 1943-1944 (Box 196, Folder 46)
  - Gasoline rationing, 1943 (Box 196, Folder 47)
  - G.I. Bill, 1944 (Box 196, Folder 48)
  - Governor's Reconversion Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 196, Folder 49)
  - Hansen, Ralph, undated (Box 196, Folder 50)
  - Hartford Courant: Industrial Review, 1944 January 23 (Box 196, Folder 51)
  - Hartford office materials, 1943-1944 (Box 196, Folder 52)
  - Housatonic Valley Parkway: Mr. Lay, 1944 (Box 197, Folder 53)
  - Kohn, F. Corbin: Assistant Director, 1944-1945 (Box 197, Folder 54)
  - Legislative Committee report, 1944 December 20 (Box 197, Folder 55)
  - Liaison Committee, undated (Box 197, Folder 56)
  - Meetings, 1943-1945 (Box 197, Folder 57-59)
  - Meeting: consideration of interim and preliminary reports, 1944 July 12 (Box 197, Folder 60)
  - Meeting, 1945 February 28 (Box 197, Folder 61)
  - Membership and Committee lists, 1943-1944 (Box 197, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1944 (Box 197, Folder 63)
  - National Planning Association, 1944 June (Box 197, Folder 64)
  - New England Council: report of special committee on ownership and finance, undated (Box 197, Folder 65)
  - "New Haven's Problems" by Arnold Guyot Dana, 1937 July (Box 197, Folder 66)